sharesome.com 2008-05-13

# Privacy & Security | Dale and Thomas Popcorn

|   
|    

|   
| 

| 

| Home > | Customer Service > |  Privacy & Security  
---|---|---  
  
**Back to** Customer Service main page  
  
##  PRIVACY & SECURITY

|    

Dale and ThomasTM Popcorn is committed to protecting the privacy of our online visitors. This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices governing the use of information submitted to Dale and ThomasTM Popcorn through this web site.

The Information We Collect  
If you decide to become a registered user or receive updates from this site, you will be asked to provide us with certain information including, for example, a valid email address and credit card number for billing purposes. We collect your contact information so that we can process your order and provide you with the information you request. Additionally, we collect IP addresses, domain names when provided by visitors and aggregate information on pages visited as well as information volunteered by consumers in interactive elements such as polls. The credit card information collected is strictly used for billing purposes. If you have any questions about billing or service, you are welcome to address them by contacting info@daleandthomaspopcorn.com. Please be aware that our site contains links to other sites and that privacy practices of these other sites may differ from those of Dale and ThomasTM Popcorn. Each site is responsible for its own privacy practices.

Information Usage and Sharing  
Dale and ThomasTM Popcorn values your patronage and respects your right to privacy. Because we are committed to protecting your privacy, personal data relating to an identified or identifiable individual that is submitted to this web page will be collected, processed stored, and disposed of in accordance with applicable U.S. law. However, U.S. law may not provide the degree of protection to personal data, which is available in other countries. The submission of personal data constitutes the User's acknowledgement that he/she has read and understood this notice, and agrees to its terms. In order to facilitate the purchase of goods online or to update visitors of new products or services, Dale and ThomasTM Popcorn may share certain individual information with our partners. Additionally, personal and individual information will be shared with third parties if contest registrants check, or do not un-check the boxes on the Contest Registration page. Dale and ThomasTM Popcorn may share non-personal, non-individual information in aggregate form with unaffiliated third parties for marketing or research purposes. Should our records be subpoenaed, we will act in accordance with our legal counsel's advice and handle each matter on a case-by-case basis. In connection with any contest or promotion, Dale and ThomasTM Popcorn reserves the right to post all information regarding contest and promotion winners that may be legally required or as is otherwise disclosed in the contest rules. 

**Updating your Account/Dale and Thomas TM Popcorn Opt-Out policy  
**We require subscribers holding accounts on our site to permit us to communicate with them regarding their accounts. If you are a subscriber you consent to receiving e-mail from Dale and ThomasTM Popcorn. Our site provides all users and subscribers the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from our partners. In addition, you may request not to be contacted by our partners in connection with any new services, updates, or promotions. After becoming a subscriber you may request the removal of your name from a partners mailing list by contacting them directly. We also give users the following additional options for removing or updating their information from our database:  
You can send email to [info@daleandthomaspopcorn.com](mailto:info@daleandthomaspopcorn.com)  
You can send mail to the following postal address:  
Dale and ThomasTM Popcorn  
One Cedar Lane  
Englewood, NJ 07631

Cookies   
Dale and ThomasTM Popcorn uses cookie technology to increase the ease of use of the web site. When you make selections or set preferences on our site, the site will send a request to your browser to record some of your selections in a "cookie" file. The cookie is a small text file that resides on your hard drive. From time to time, our site will request the cookie from your browser so we can retrieve the stored information and you do not have to repeatedly enter information. Should you choose not to accept these cookies you may not be able to use portions of our site.

Dale and ThomasTM Popcorn never uses cookies to store credit card information, nor is the information we store in the cookie intended to be read by any other web site.

Many browsers allow users to set the preferences to show a warning each time a cookie request is received. You can also set most browsers not to accept cookies at all.

At times, some of the advertisers on our site set cookies when you select their ad banner. We do not receive the data collected by those cookies.

Security   
Dale and ThomasTM Popcorn has security measures in place to safeguard against the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. By making your bids and or purchases through our secure server, you are protected by Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") technology, used by most browsers, including Netscape and Microsoft Explorer. This technology allows us to utilize advanced encryption in order to protect the information transmitted between your computer and our server. Through encryption, the personal information you enter, including your name and credit card information, is securely dispatched over the Internet.

Policy Changes  
As Dale and ThomasTM Popcorn grows and new features are added or legal requirements change, this privacy policy may be modified. Although all information submitted to Dale and ThomasTM Popcorn is subject to the terms and conditions of this policy and any modifications, you may remove or restrict access to your account by updating your account information at www.daleandthomaspopcorn.com. Any changes to the Dale and ThomasTM Popcorn privacy policy will be posted online.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at [info@daleandthomaspopcorn.com](mailto:info@daleandthomaspopcorn.com)

1-800-POPCORN® is a registered trademark.

| 

0 total item(s) 

|   
|
